https://www.funteambuilding.com/copyright-privacy-policy-terms-use/

Copyright
All rights reserved. No part of the FunTeamBuilding.com web site may be reproduced by any means without written permission. For example, your possession of a copy of a digitized image does not in itself mean you have any rights to use it. For information regard the use of any material on this site, e-mail Fun Team Building. Furthermore, any content not created by or specifically for FunTeamBuilding.com is assumed to be within the realm of the Public’s Right of “Fair Use” and no copyright infringement is intended.
Privacy Policy
We also have the highest regard for your privacy. FunTeamBuilding.com does not sell, rent, loan or transfer any personal information regarding visitors to any of our sites to any unrelated third parties. Examples of personal information that may be collected includes full name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number. Personal information you give us is held with the utmost care and security and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented.
Terms of Use
By visiting and using the FunTeamBuilding.com web site you agree to these terms and conditions. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We reserve the right to make changes to our site and these disclaimers, terms, and conditions at any time. We also reserve the right to refuse service in its discretion, including, without limitation, if FunTeamBuilding.com believes that visitor conduct violates applicable law or is harmful to the interests of FunTeamBuilding.com.
Disclaimer
THIS SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASIS. FUNTEAMBUILDING.COM MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THE SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.
Search for:
Achieve Professional Fulfillment Through Attitude and Purpose
The Skinny On Making the Best of Commuter Traffic
The Essence of Leadership is the Success of Others
Work Better, Feel Better by Moving More at Work
Dispelling the Myth to Achieve a Realistic Work Life Balance
Master Plan to Deal with Coworker Personality Conflicts
